http://www.irongloves.com/privacy-policy.html

HomeVideosCustom LogoContact Us Log in
Register
0
AccessoriesBat WarmersBottle GlovesGripp BallsIron CoversPutter CoversRifle Scope CoversDog Awareness Letters
Home › Privacy Policy Privacy Policy
Email Privacy Policy
We have created this email privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information.
Why did you receive an email from us?
If you received a mailing from us, (a) your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("opt-in"), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.
How we protect your privacy
We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system.
Sharing and Usage
We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.
Home
About Us
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Return Policy
Contact Us
Drop Ship Agreement
© 2005 - 2020 Iron Gloves, Inc, all rights reserved.
Web Design by BX3 Interactive
Hide
My Cart
Your cart is empty.
